Guide to the Washington State University Theatre and Dance Records 1924-2011
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Theatre and Dance Records
1924-2011
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 387
Washington State University. School of Music and Theatre Arts
5.5 Linear feet of shelf space 13 Boxes
Programs and photographs from theatrical productions produced by Washington State University from the 1920s to 2010s. Also included are departmental papers, programs from regional theatre groups, and student theses.
The Department of Speech of Washington State University, established in 1923, has produced numerous plays since 1925 as a function of that department. Maynard Lee Daggy headed the Speech Department from its inception in 1923 until 1946 and directed many of the earlier productions. Departmental theatrical finances, publicity, and publications were the responsibility of the University Theatre office located in Bryan Hall. In the early 1970s a new site for University Theatre productions and the Department of Speech was constructed and subsequently named Daggy Hall. Circa 1988-1989, theatre was moved from Speech and joined with the Department of Music to create the School of Music and Theatre Arts. In 2008, Theatre Arts and Dance were separated from Music, and in May of 2011 the Department of Theatre and Dance closed as a result of budget cuts.
In addition to regular theatre productions, special production units including Children's Theatre, Stage II Productions, Final Stage, The Black Ensemble, Pullman's New Summer Palace, and Stage One have existed. With the exception of Summer Palace, most of these appear to have been sporadic, and were occasionally short lived.
The majority of the collection is programs, photographs, and other documents relating to theatrical productions produced by the State College of Washington (later Washington State University) theater programs, dating from the very first productions (1924) to the very last (2011). This collection is more or less supplemental to the previously existing collections (see Related Materials), but includes the only known photographs and programs of many of WSC’s earliest productions, and of many of the later supporting performance groups. A number of non-final theses and student papers are included, many of which detail aspects of WSU’s theater performances.
Series 1: Papers, Programs, and Photographs is divided into three subseries: Subseries 1.1 is WSU theatre programs, photographs, and documents; Subseries 1.2 consists of departmental papers and photographs, and programs from other performance programs, including the WSU Theatre-affiliated Summer Palace; Subseries 1.3 is student papers, primarily Masters Theses which lack documentation certifying them as accepted. Some may indeed be final copies, but they may also be drafts or unaccepted theses. The students in this subseries are only those for whom the Libraries did not already hold an official copy.
Series 2: Card-mounted photographs, 1949-1968 and compact discs, 2003-2011and consists of two format-based subseries: Subseries 2.1 is card-mounted photographs from WSU Office of University Publications and Printing; Subseries 2.2 is CDs of performance photographs.
Series 3: Scrapbooks, 1943-1972 consists of oversized scrapbooks.
Researchers should be aware that due to the format-based series structure of this collection, materials from a given production could potentially be found in all three series.
The collection is arranged in a number of series and subseries, the first level of which is based on format and item size.
Series 1 is broken into subject based subseries: Subseries 1.1 is ordered chronologically; Subseries 1.2 is organized alphabetically by subject; Subseries 1.3 is arranged alphabetically by student name.
Series 2 consists of two format-based subseries: Subseries 2.1 is maintained in their original numerical, and mostly chronological, order; Subseries 2.2 is also maintained in chronological order.
The digital materials in this collection were copied over into the MASC’s non-public digital storage during processing for preservation purposes.
This collection is open and available for research use.
The papers of the WSU Theatre and Dance program were transferred to the Washington State University Libraries’ Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collection on June 29, 2018, by Gail Siegel of WSU Performing Arts, and retained as UA2018-09. The materials had been stored in an informal departmental library for decades prior.
The Theatre program’s working library of books was transferred to the WSU Libraries at the same time; those are now in the public stacks and are not part of MASC’s holdings.
Some materials were moved to Washington State University Publications 48: Visual and Performing and Literary Arts Committee (VPLAC) / Performing Arts
One professor’s collection of 1950-1952 Northwestern University programs was transferred to that school’s archives.
State College of Washington Theatre Records, 1925-1965 (Archives 42)
Washington State University Theatre Records, 1965-1978 (Archives 105)
Washington State University Theatre Records, 1966-1981 (Archives 209)
Washington State University Theatre Records, 1979-1986 (Archives 251)
Washington State University Theatre and Dance Records, 1980-2011 (Archives 308)
Washington State University Publications: Theatre Posters, 1957-2011 (WSU 112)
Washington State University Theatre Slides, 1950-2001 (PC 146)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. School of Music and Theatre Arts -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. University Theatre -- Records and correspondence; State College of Washington. University Theatre -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. Department of Theatre and Dance -- Records and correspondence; State College of Washington. University Theatre; Washington State University. University Theatre; Washington State University. Department of Theatre and Dance
College and school drama, American -- Washington (State) -- Pullman -- Records and correspondence; Theater -- Washington (State) -- Pullman -- Records and correspondence
Performing Arts; Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- Series 1: Papers, Photographs, and Programs, 1924-2002.
  - Subseries 1.1: WSU Theatre & other campus performances, 1924-1991.
    - Miss Lulu Bett. Program, Photograph. April 1924. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Country Cousin. Photograph. Dec. 1924. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Programs: Stuart Walker's Portmanteau Theatre; Everyman; A Full House; Mrs. Bumpstead-Leigh; The Intimate Strangers; Kempy (Moroni Olsen Players). 1924. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - You and I (Moroni Olsen Players). Program. Jan. 1925. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Successful Calamity. Photographs. May 1925. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The First Year. Program, photographs. Summer 1925. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Rivals. Program, papers, photographs. Dec. 1925. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Programs: Icebound; One Acts: White Elephants, The Valiant. 1925. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Goose Hangs High. Photographs. April 1926. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Three Wise Fools. Photograph. Oct. 1926. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Love in a Mist. Program, photograph. March 1928. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Programs: Expressing Willie; The Champion. 1928. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Loose Ankles. Photograph. Feb. 1929. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Programs: The Haunted House; The Patsy. 1929. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Coed and the Brute. Photograph. 1930. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - A Full House. Photographs. March 1933. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Programs: Journey's End; Hold Everything; A Character Intrudes; The Dance of Life; The Love Expert. 1934. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Big Hearted Herbert. Program and photographs. Feb. 1935. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Spider and the Fly. Program. June 1935. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Gammer Gurton's Needle. Photographs. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Gratitude. Photograph. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Little Prison. Photograph. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Sows Ear. Photograph. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ten Room Cottage. Photograph. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - The Winner. Photograph. July 1937. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - The Elopement. Photograph. Aug. 1937. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - A Little Learning. Photograph. Aug. 1937. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - On a Sunday. Photograph. July 1939. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - The Hairy Ape. Photographs. March 1941. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Ladies in Retirement. Program, photograph. July 1942. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Star Bound. Photographs. May 1944. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Letters to Lucerne. Program. July 1944. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - The Old Ladies. Photograph, program. July 1945. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Lecture Program Series on High-School Dramatics. July 1945. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Programs: Home of the Brave; A Reading Hour; Man and the Masses; Grace Newell Faculty Recital; One Acts: The Neighbors, The Wedding, For the Love of Allah, Hello Out There. 1948. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Programs: The International Inn; The Rivals (UW Touring Theatre); One Acts: The Same Old Thing, The Late Christopher Bean, The Pot Boiler. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Season playlists, programs: For the Love of Lou; Say No More. 1950. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Blackouts of '51. Program. May 1951. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Programs: The Telephone; The Medium; Sailing of the Nancy Belle; Down in the Valley; The Beautiful People; The Skin of Our Teeth; Figures of Fire. 1953. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Programs: International Festival Week; Philip Hanson Reading Recital; Taming of the Shrew (Readers Theater). 1954. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Season playlist, program: Electra. 1956. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Programs: One Acts: Could-Burst, The Powers That Be, Hot Lemonade, The Lord's Will, The Purple Door Knob, Hangs Over Thy Head, A Phoenix Too Frequent. 1957. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Programs: Man and Superman; One Acts: Minnie Field, Five Days, The Potboiler. 1958. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Programs: The Fifth Column; Punchinello. 1959. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Season playlist, program: Carousel. 1960. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Season playlist, programs: Pride and Prejudice (Readers Theater); Festival of Dance and Gymnastics; Dame Judith Anderson in Scenes from Macbeth, Tower Beyond Tragedy, Medea. 1961. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Season playlist, unidentified photographs, programs: The Curious Savage; Pygmalion (Readers Theater); Arsenic and Old Lace; The Princess and the Swineherd. 1962. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Readers Theater clipping, program: Under Milk Wood. 1963. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Programs: A Resounding Tinkle; The Weather-Man's Secret; The Rehearsal; The Women; Antigone. 1964. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Programs: Look Back in Anger; A Resounding Tinkle; Springtime for Henry; The American Dream; The Lesson; One Acts: Are Men Superior?, The Monkey's Paw, The Egotist, Hello Out There, Why Girls Stay Home, Masks of Angels; Of Mice and Men (National Collegiate Players). 1965. (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Programs: My Partner; Ten Nights in a Bar-Room; East Lynne; Ten Little Indians; The Miser (Olympic College Players); Joey; Daniel Boone; The Taming of the Shrew; The Dot and the Line & Winnie-the-Pooh (Readers Theater); One Acts: Before Breakfast, Fingerbowls and Araminta, Objections Overruled, The American Dream; Double Talk & Archy and Mehitable (Readers Theater); The Dramatic Silence; One Acts: Hot Lemonade, Mimsy were the Borogroves; One Acts: A Bedtime Story, The Bald Soprano, Crawling Arnold, The Last of my Solid Gold Watches, Sham; Lysistrata; Waiting for Godot; Outward Bound; Summer Palace season program / fan. 1966. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Summer Palace scrapbook of photographs, clippings, programs, and ephemera. 1966-1967. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Season playlist, programs: One acts: Weatherwise, The Zoo Story, Marriage Proposal; Marat/Sade; Any Wednesday; Night Must Fall; One acts: Holding a Husband, This Property is Condemned, Before we Were; An Experiment in Drama: The Sparrow, The Twilight of the Aardvark, An Oration Against Ice Boxes; Lovers and Madmen; One acts: The 9:00 Mail, To Soften Rocks, The Pointed Stick; The Count of Monte Cristo; The Octoroon; Davy Crockett; The Playboy of the Western World. 1967. (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Three Penny Opera. Photographs. Jan. 1968. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Miss Julie. Photographs. April 1968. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Summer Palace scrapbook of photographs, clippings, programs, and ephemera. 1968. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Season playlist, Dramacard, clippings, and programs: The In-Between Key; Silverheels; Miss Julie; Many Moons; Lady Audley's Secret; Richard III; In White America; Hansel and Gretel; Llluuv; The Introduction; Portrait of a Madonna; The Ugly Duckling; Christmas Package. 1968. (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Scrapbook of photographs, clippings and, programs. 1968-1969. (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Programs: Family Christmas Package; One acts: Hughie, The Hungerers, The Sandbox; One acts: The Zoo Story, The Unexpurgated Memories of Bernard Mergendeiler, Crawling Arnold. 1969. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - One acts: Conquest of Everett, Chamber Music, The Questioning of Nick. Photographs, program. Jan. 1970. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Season playlists, programs: Creative Dramatics Variety Show; Reynard the Fox; Brother, You're Next; student directing projects. 1970. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Summer Palace scrapbook of facility and backstage photographs. 1971 ca. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season playlists, programs: The Enchanted Night; A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum; Franny and Zooey; student acting/directing projects. 1971. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season playlist, programs, misc. photographs: Christmas Takes a Bough (Readers Theater); Christopher Sly; The White House (Readers Theater). 1972. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Programs, announcements: Breakfast of Champions (Readers Theater); What It Is (Black Readers Theater); Charley's Aunt, inc. review clipping; student acting/directing projects. 1973. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Programs, announcements: Longbeard the Wizard, The Dragon the Lived Under Manhattan (Readers Theater); Joie de Vivre - Sometimes (Readers Theater); Murder in the Cathedral (Readers Theater); Northwest Drama Conference; student acting/directing projects. 1974. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Season playlist, programs: Virtue's Reward, Spoon River Anthology (Readers Theater); Agamemnon (Readers Theater); Carl Sandburg Sings America (Readers Theater); God's Trombones; Story Theatre; Edgar Allan Poe His Stories and Poems; student acting/directing projects. 1975. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Programs: The Taming of the Shrew (Young Vic Company); Feiffer's People, White House (Readers Theater); The Ballad of Baby Doe; The Comedies of Neil Simon (Readers Theater); Dear Liar (Readers Theater); student acting/directing projects. 1976. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Programs: Radio Relived (Readers Theater); White Memoir (Eclectic Union Theatre); 6 Rms Riv Vu (Readers Theater); Seascape (Readers Theater); The Tingalary Bird; Born Yesterday; Out of the Flying Pan; Not I. 1977. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Man of La Mancha. Photographs. June 1978. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Summer Palace photographs. 1978. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Season playlist, programs: Trinity (Readers Theater); Medea a Noh Cycle (Readers Theater); Radio Relived (Readers Theater); Paper Flowers; Christmas program; Reel Theatre. 1978. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Programs: Pacific Northwest Poets; Robert Patrick; Developing the Self (Readers Theater); War of the Worlds (Readers Theater); Three Plays for Mother (Readers Theatre). 1980. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Summer Palace photographs. 1980. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Clipping: James and the Giant Peach. 1990. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Theatre awards ballot, poster: The Shadow of a Doubt. 1991. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Subseries 1.2: Departmental papers and photographs, and programs from other performing organizations, 1924-2001.
    - American College Theatre Festival XVI, Pullman, WA. Feb. 1984. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Attendance data, 1946-1953. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bryan Hall Theater - Supervision and operation, 1955-1988. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - The Commedians. Papers, photographs. 1969-1973. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Daggy Hall planning, 1967 ca. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Daggy Hall - Design Development Drawings, 1968 ca. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Photographs: portraits. Likely of Speech/Theatre majors. 1960s-1970s. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Photographs: students, class, and backstage. Undated. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Photographs: WSU productions. Unidentified and undated. (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Playlists. 1928-1967. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Production budgets. 1984. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Programs: Community Concert Association. 1948-1951. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Programs: High School Summer Camp, 1935-1971. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Programs: Pullman Community Theatre. 1954-1979. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Programs: Pullman High School and other Whitman County K-12s. 1924-1971. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Programs: Regional performances. 1931-1991. (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
    - Programs: Touring opera, orchestra, music companies. 1963-1978. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Programs: University of Idaho. 1949-1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Programs: WSU Department of Music. 1924-1977. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Programs: WSU Pullman Artist Series / Lecture Artist Series. 1954-1979. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Summer Palace. Photographs. Unidentified and undated. (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - WSU Theatre Program Handbook, Undergrad. Ed. 2000-2001. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Subseries 1.3: Student Papers, 1960-2002.
    - Anderson, Lauren Kay. Aristophanes' Lysistrata. A Victorian adaptation based on the American Civil War. 1998. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Ashworth, Lillian. Medea, and it's place in history: a criticism. 1960. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Baker, Max. Developing a script. 1992. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bowers, Dale. Diamond Studs: the Life of Jesse James. A musical comedy by Jim Wann and Bland Simpson. 1980. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Don C. Mixed Nuts and beyond: A consideration of student directed one-act evenings at W.S.U. 1991. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Don C. The Terrorists: A portable design. 1991. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Destefano, Scott C. Project notebook: Heaven Can Wait. 1982. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Drew, Susan. Historical perspective on the American minstrel era. 1992. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Ebert, Frederick T. Five nineteenth century illusions updated for modern stage effects. 1985. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Feathers, Marianne Straughan. Costuming Stop the World I Want to Get Off. 1974. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Fenton, Karen. A survey of speech and drama in accredited Idaho high schools 1966-1967. 1968 ca. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Fogelberg-Billette, Cheryl. Senior adult theatre. 1990. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Gallo, Colleen. Reflections of the human spirit: the analysis and production of Joanna M. Glass' Canadian Gothic. 1991. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Harrison, Susan B. The Miracle Worker: A director's journey. 1993. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Johnston, William J. The composition and history of Silverheels. 1968. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Lane, L.D. The use of a four-phase rehearsal method. Based upon Dr. Rollo May's description of the creative process. 1987. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Maxfield. T. Christopher. Theatre as an educational tool: seminars, workshop and production utilizing Oscar Wilde's The Importance of Being Earnest. 1994. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - McClaskey, William. The singer-actor: a performer with two brains. 1985 ca. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Michener, Dee Wills. A Moon for the Misbegotten: criticism and production. 1970. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Nice, Brent Robert. Reflections of a civilization: American culture in Samuel Beckett's Endgame. 1991. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Quinley, Virginia. Project report: theatre workshop for high school teachers. 1982. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Richmond, Janet. Moonnot August: A new play produced in a premier performance. 1996. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Rohrbacher, Richard Willard. The In-Between Key, a play in three acts. 1968. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ronning, Cassandra Jane. Costuming The Playboy of the Western World: the theory and practice. 1968. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Rosefeldt, Margaret Waltzer. Costuming Peter Pan: the theory and practice. 1974. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sampson, David. Digital conversion and presentation of the 77 years of the Washington State University School of Theatre Arts performance archive (includes CDs). 2002. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Schwarz, Lyle Allen. Augustin Daly's Horizon: criticism and production. 1970. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Swan, John D. Peter Shaffer's The Private Ear and The Public Eye: production and evaluation. 1978. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Thelen, Lawrence. The Third Wave: from short story to music play; the process of adapting literature for the stage. 1993. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Trapp, Richard James. Bar Exercise: a play in three acts. 1972. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Series 2: Card-mounted photographs, 1949-1968 and compact discs, 2003-2011.
  - Subseries 2.1: WSU Office of Publications and Printing card-mounted photographs, 1949-1968.
    - No. 02584b (1949) - no. 50094 (1964); no. 00079 (1964) - no. 03554 (1965). (Box 8)
    - No. 05927 (1967) - no. 09724 (1968); no. 00042 (1968) - no. 00287 (1968). (Box 9)
  - Subseries 2.2: CDs of production photographs, 2003-2011.
    - Five Women Wearing the Same Dress. 2003. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Equus. 2003. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Six Degrees of Separation. 2004. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Taming of the Shrew. 2004. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Crimes of the Heart. 2004. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Stage One. 2004. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Death and the King's Horsemen. 2005. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Last of the Formicans. 2005. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Romeo and Juliet. 2005. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Stage One. 2005. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Dragonwings. 2006. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - The Elephant Man. 2006. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - A Lie of the Mind. 2006. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Stage One. 2006. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - The Golden Age. 2007. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - The Miss Firecracker Content. 2007. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Titus Andronicus. 2007. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Stage One: Layover; Reunion; Pouring Rain; Duel. 2007. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Passion. 2008. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sylvia. 2008. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - The Exonerated. 2008. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - The Exonerated (video). 2008. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Hedda Gabler. 2008. (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
    - Hedda Gabler (video). 2008. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Stage One. 2008. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Raised in Captivity. 2009. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - The Heidi Chronicles. 2009. (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Dracula. 2009. (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
    - The Glass Menagerie. 2010. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - End Days. 2010. (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
    - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. 2010. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Stage One. 2010. (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Play it Again, Sam. 2011. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - The Shape of Things. 2011. (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Series 3: Scrapbooks, 1943-1972.
  - Photographs, programs, and clippings (brown-cover album). 1943-1949. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, photographs, ands programs (spiral bound album). Jan.-June, 1947. (Box 10, Folder 2)